twilightersanonymous.com 2012-11-25

# Privacy | Twilighters Anonymous

This privacy statement covers TwilightersAnonymous.com (â€œTwilighters Anonymousâ€). Please read this statement carefully before using proceeding to access TwilightersAnonymous.com. Your use of TwilightersAnonymous.com indicates your agreement to abide by the Terms in effect.

**Information Collection**  
TwilightersAnonymous.com is the sole owner of the information collected on TwilightersAnonymous.com. TwilightersAnonymous.com may collect information from our users at several points in the site. We recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit TwilightersAnonymous.com, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

**Comments**  
In order to enhance their use of the TwilightersAnonymous.com, users can choose to leave comments on particular articles of interest. TwilightersAnonymous.com currently uses a third-party application, Disqus, to manage comments the website.Â  Additional information may be collected by Disqus. You may read their privacy policy [here](http://disqus.com/privacy-policy/ "here"). If a third party complains that a comment breaches our Terms of Service (e.g. libels them), then in accordance with our Terms, we will make reasonable efforts to contact the commenter to give them the opportunity to respond to such requests. Please refer to our Terms of Use for more information.Â  We do not make it a policy to delete comments, and will do so, only as a last resort.

**Mailing Lists**  
TwilightersAnonymous.com may launch a mailing list, in order to provide subscribers with relevant information â€“ breaking news, or weekly or daily round-ups, for example. In order to sign up to receive regular emails from a siteâ€™s mailing list, users must submit information including a valid email address and demographic information such as location and interests. This information will be used in aggregate form only in order to assess general user interest in various internal and third party products and services, and your personal and contact information will not be passed to any other organization.

**Cookies**  
TwilightersAnonymous.com may use cookies. A cookie is a piece of data stored on the userâ€™s computer tied to information about the user. We may use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. For the session ID cookie, once users close the browser, the cookie simply terminates. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on the user?s hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions.

You can configure your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set. If you reject all cookies, you will not be able to use any TwilightersAnonymous.com products or services that require you to â€œsign in,â€ and you may not be able to take full advantage of all offerings. However, not all TwilightersAnonymous.coms services require that you accept cookies.

**Third Party Cookies**  
Some of our business partners may use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, TwilightersAnonymous.com has no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by TwilightersAnonymous.com only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Google Advertising**  
Some ads appearing on this Web site are delivered to users by Google, among other services. Information about usersâ€™ visits to this site, such as number of times they have viewed an ad (but not username, date of birth, or any other personal information), is used to serve Google ads to users on this site. For more information about Google and cookies, please click here.

**Links**  
TwilightersAnonymous.com contains links to other sites. Please be aware that TwilightersAnonymous.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by TwilightersAnonymous.com.

**Log Files**  
Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. We may use a tracking utility that uses log files to analyze user movement.

**Business Transitions**  
In the event TwilightersAnonymous.com goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of a portion of its assets, usersâ€™ personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred.

**Legal Disclaimer**  
Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, TwilightersAnonymous.com may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on TwilightersAnonymous.com.

**Notification of Changes**  
Whenever TwilightersAnonymous.com changes its privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

**Contact Information**  
If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please use the following methods:

email: Â newsblog AT TwilightersAnonymous DOT com

Post Office Mail:  
TwilightersAnonymous.com  
c/oÂ Akira Creative Group, Inc.  
5055 Business Center Drive Suite 108-247  
Fairfield, CA 94534

Phone: (661) 252-6630  
Fax: (661) 878-7187 

Online Contact Form: [CLICK HERE](http://twilightersanonymous.com/contact-us)
